A Guide to the Papers of Henry Heth, 1765-1800
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Agreement between Harry Heth and Daniel French 1811 Nov 30 (Box 6)
- Letter from Robert Cambell to Harry Heth 1811 Dec 3 (Box 6)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1811 Dec 9 (Box 6)
- Letter from Joseph Luman Bishop to Harry Heth 1811 Dec 10 (Box 6)
- Letter from Luman Bishop to Harry Heth 1811 Dec 10 (Box 6)
- Letter from Richard Brooke to Harry Heth 1811 Dec 11 (Box 6)
- Letter from Robert Campbell to Harry Heth 1811 Dec 14 (Box 6)
- Letter from Samuel Dyers to Harry Heth 1811 Dec 16 (Box 6)
- Letter from S. M. Bradferd to Harry Heth 1811 Dec 16 (Box 6)
- Letter from D. Street to Harry Heth 1811 Dec 24 (Box 6)
- Letter from David Patterson to Harry Heth 1811 Dec 26 (Box 6)
- Accounts and receipts for 1811 1811 (Box 6)
- Bill of sale-Robert Hill to Harry Heth 1812 Jan 8 (Box 6)
- Letter from D. Thomas to Henry Heth, Jr. 1812 Jan 8 (Box 6)
- Bill of sale-Edward Digges to Harry Heth 1812 Jan 9 (Box 6)
- Letter from John R. Archer to Harry Heth 1812 Jan 15 (Box 6)
- Memorandum between Harry Heth & Samuel Wooddy 1812 Jan 21 (Box 6)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Mrs. J. Nicolson 1812 Jan 28 (Box 6)
- Letter from W. P. Pembleton to Harry Heth 1812 Feb 2 (Box 6)
- Letter from John Marshall to Harry Heth 1812 Mar 2 (Box 6)
- Letter from John Railey & Harry Heth 1812 Mar 7 (Box 6)
- William LaPrade vs. Cundiffe & Heth 1812 Mar 16 (Box 6)
- Agreement between Elizabeth Railey, John Railey, & Harry Heth 1812 Mar 16 (Box 6)
- Letter from Williamson & Watkins to Harry Heth 1812 Mar 18 (Box 6)
- Letter from John Cundiffe to Harry Heth 1812 Mar 21 (Box 6)
- Letter from Harry Heth to John Cundiffe 1812 Mar 21 (Box 6)
- Letter from Harry Heth to John Cundiffe 1812 Mar 21 (Box 6)
- Papers relating to the boundaries dispute of Black Heath 1812 Mar 23 (Box 6)
- Letter from William Pope to Harry Heth 1812 Apr 4 (Box 6)
- Letter from Samuel Cullen to Jordan Martin 1812 Apr 5 (Box 6)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1812 Apr 11 (Box 6)
- Agreement between Harry Heth, Robert Gordon, & James Currie concerning Falling-Creek coal mine 1812 Apr 30 (Box 6)
- Letter from Harry Randolph to Harry Heth 1812 May 18 (Box 6)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1812 Jun 15 (Box 6)
- Letter from Harry Randolph to Harry Heth 1812 Jun 11 (Box 6)
- Agreement between Harry Heth& Matthew Burfoote 1812 Jun 16 (Box 6)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Thomas Railey 1812 Jul 7 (Box 6)
- Letter from [?] to Harry Heth 1812 Jul 26 (Box 6)
- Letter from Beverley Randolph to Lavinia Randolph 1812 Jul 27 (Box 6)
- Letter from Beverley Randolph to Lavinia Randolph 1812 Aug 1 (Box 6)
- Letter from Beverley Randolph to Lavinia Randolph 1812 Aug 8 (Box 6)
- Letter from Harriet C. Robbins to Mrs. Randolph 1812 Aug 13 (Box 6)
- Letter from George Williamson to Harry Heth 1812 Aug 26 (Box 6)
- Letter from Beverley Randolph to Lavinia Randolph 1812 Aug 30 (Box 6)
- Memorandum from Harry Heth to William Hay 1812 Aug 31 (Box 6)
- Letter from N. Sanders to Harry Heth 1812 Sep 16 (Box 6)
- Memorandum of Agreement between Peter Porter & Harry Heth 1812 Sep 24 (Box 6)
- Letter from H. Heth 1812 Oct 12 (Box 6)
- Letter from Rebecca Harris to Mrs. Lavinia Randolph 1812 Nov 7 (Box 6)
- Agreement between Harry Heth & Archibald Woodbridge 1812 Dec 21 (Box 6)
- Letter from William Hay, Jr., to Charles Copeland 1812 Dec 21 (Box 6)
- Letter from Wade Mosby to Harry Heth 1812 Dec 22 (Box 6)
- Letter from H. G. Heth to Harry Heth 1812 Dec 27 (Box 6)
- Letter from John Stevens to Harry Heth 1812 Dec 31 (Box 6)
- Accounts and receipts for 1812 1812 (Box 6)
- Letter from I. Salle to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 6 (Box 6)
- Letter from William Vadin to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 6 (Box 6)
- Letter from Richard Brooke to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 6 (Box 6)
- Letter from Hannah F. Wells to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 7 (Box 6)
- Letter from Nathaniel Harrison to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 7 (Box 7)
- Letter from N. Ellicott to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 8 (Box 7)
- Letter from William C. Copeland to William Hay 1813 Jan 11 (Box 7)
- Letter from William C. Copeland to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 13 (Box 7)
- Letter from Thomas Mann Randolph to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 16 (Box 7)
- Letter from Joseph & Edward Mayo to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 17 (Box 7)
- Letter from Peter F. Smith to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 19 (Box 7)
- Letter from E. D. Digges to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 19 (Box 7)
- Letter from Peter Deffarges to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 20 (Box 7)
- Letter from Thomas Jefferson to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 20 (Box 7)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Messrs. Heth and Randolph 1813 Jan 22 (Box 7)
- Letter from Robert Pleasants to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 22 (Box 7)
- Letter from Wade Mosely to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 23 (Box 7)
- Letter from John Stevens to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 26 (Box 7)
- Letter from John Davidson to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 27 (Box 7)
- Letter from John E. Meade to Harry Heth 1813 Jan 29 (Box 7)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Thomas Taylor 1813 Jan 31 (Box 7)
- Letter from Christ. Thompkins, Jr., to Harry Heth 1813 Feb 7 (Box 7)
- Letter from Jane Hill to Harry Heth 1813 Mar 14 (Box 7)
- Letter from Harry Heth to William Hay, Jr. 1813 Mar 27 (Box 7)
- Statements and Memorandums for C. B. Page 1813 Apr (Box 7)
- Letter from Charles and R. Railey to Harry Heth 1813 Apr 12 (Box 7)
- List of furniture and clothing 1813 Apr 13 (Box 7)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1813 Apr 30 (Box 7)
- Letter from Thomas Miller to Harry Heth 1813 May 2 (Box 7)
- Letter from Christopher Thompkins to Harry Heth 1813 May 8 (Box 7)
- Letter from Payroll of the Manchester Cavalry 1813 May 13 (Box 7)
- Letter from John Myers to Harry Heth 1813 May 15 (Box 7)
- Letter from John T. Banand to Harry Heth 1813 May 15 (Box 7)
- Letter from W. Hampton to Harry Heth 1813 May 18 (Box 7)
- Letter from John H. Cocke to Harry Heth 1813 May 18 (Box 7)
- Letter from William Pennock to Harry Heth 1813 May 18 (Box 7)
- Letter from James Scott to Harry Heth 1813 May 19 (Box 7)
- Letter from A. Lawshill to Harry Heth 1813 May 24 (Box 7)
- Letter from William Pennock to Harry Heth 1813 May 27 (Box 7)
- Letter from John Tayloe to Harry Heth 1813 May 30 (Box 7)
- Letter from Thomas Mann Randolph to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 3 (Box 7)
- Letter from W. Hampton to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 4 (Box 7)
- Letter from Charles McGill to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 5 (Box 7)
- Letter from William Ball to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 7 (Box 7)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 8 (Box 7)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Thomas Mann Randolph 1813 Jun 8 (Box 7)
- Letter from John Vest to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 9 (Box 7)
- Letter from Thomas Mann Randolph to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 12 (Box 7)
- Letter from Stilwaggon and Knight to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 12 (Box 7)
- Letter from Charles L. Stewart to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 14 (Box 7)
- Letter from Oliver Evans to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 15 (Box 7)
- Letter from Jordan Martin to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 18 (Box 7)
- Letter from Egbert Harris to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 20 (Box 7)
- Letter from Robert Brough to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 20 (Box 7)
- Letter from James Scott to Mrs. Lavinia R. Randolph 1813 Jun 25 (Box 7)
- Letter from Oliver Evans to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 26 (Box 7)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 28 (Box 7)
- Letter from A. Lannehill to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 25 (Box 7)
- Letter from J. Clarke to Harry Heth 1813 Jun 30 (Box 7)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1813 Jul (Box 7)
- Letter from Captain McLandish to Harry Heth 1813 Jul 5 (Box 7)
- Letter from William Pennock to Harry Heth 1813 Jul 10 (Box 7)
- Letter from John Myers to Harry Heth 1813 Jul 11 (Box 7)
- Letter from Robert Taylor to Harry Heth 1813 Jul 12 (Box 7)
- Letter from Oliver Evans to Harry Heth 1813 Jul 14 (Box 7)
- Letter from James Thorburn to Harry Heth 1813 Jul 15 (Box 7)
- Letter from Egbert Thomas to Harry Heth 1813 Jul 18 (Box 7)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 1813 Jul 19 (Box 7)
- Letter from William Pennock to Harry Heth 1813 Jul 21 (Box 7)
- Letter from Egbert Harris to Harry Heth 1813 Jul 20 (Box 7)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1813 Jul 28 (Box 7)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1813 Aug 20 (Box 7)
- Letter from Oliver Evans to Harry Heth 1813 Aug 3 (Box 7)
- Letter from E. Wooldridge to Harry Heth 1813 Aug 3 (Box 7)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 1813 Aug 4 (Box 7)
- Letter from Ch. G. Ridply to Harry Heth 1813 Aug 7 (Box 7)
- Letter from W. Browne to Harry Heth 1813 Aug 6 (Box 7)
- Letter from B. Randolph to Mrs. Beverly Randolph 1813 Aug 7 (Box 7)
- Letter from Mrs. Beverly Randolph to Mr. Beverly Randolph 1813 Aug 14 (Box 7)
- Letter from Robert L. Graham to Harry Heth 1813 Aug 17 (Box 7)
- Letter from Robert Nunely to Harry Heth 1813 Aug 24 (Box 7)
- Letter from Heth and Randolph to John Davidson 1813 Sep 2 (Box 7)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1813 Oct (Box 7)
- Letter from Ann F. MacKennia to Lavinia R. Randolph 1813 Nov 23 (Box 7)
- Letter from N. Ellicott to Harry Heth 1813 Dec 31 (Box 7)
- Accounts and receipts for 1813 1813 (Box 7)
- Agreement between Harry Heth and David Street 1813 (Box 7)
- Memo of Co-partnery of Harry Heth and Daniel P. Orsan 1813 (Box 7)
- Memorandum Book 1813 (Box 7)
- Letter from Mary Lawrence to Harry Heth 1814 Jan (Box 7)
- Letter from James Brown, Jr., to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 1 (Box 7)
- Letter from Thomas Miller to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 4 (Box 7)
- Agreement between David Trabue and Harry Heth 1814 Jan 6 (Box 7)
- Letter from Jon Swift to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 7 (Box 7)
- Letter from John Davidson to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 9 (Box 7)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 8 (Box 7)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Beverly Randolph 1814 Jan 10 (Box 7)
- Letter from William Hays, Jr., to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 12 (Box 7)
- Letter from A. Lannehill to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 13 (Box 7)
- Letter from Eliza Railey to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 14 (Box 7)
- Letter from J. McClung to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 14 (Box 7)
- Letter from John Tayloe to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 14 (Box 7)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 14 (Box 7)
- Harry Heth vs John Cundiffe and Cornelius Buck 1814 Jan 15 (Box 7)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Mrs. Eliza Railey 1814 Jan 19 (Box 7)
- Letter from Haley Cole to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 22 (Box 7)
- Letter from W. M. Heth to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 23 (Box 7)
- Letter from Miles King to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 22 (Box 7)
- Letter from Samuel Taylor to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 24 (Box 7)
- Letter from Eliza B. Jannelly to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 26 (Box 7)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 Jan 28 (Box 7)
- Letter from John Tidball to Harry Heth 1814 Feb 4 (Box 7)
- Letter from W. Randolph to Harry Heth 1814 Feb 6 (Box 7)
- Letter from Anderson and Watson to Harry Heth 1814 Feb 10 (Box 7)
- Letter from William G. Povale to Harry Heth 1814 Feb 15 (Box 7)
- Letter from Alex Stewart to Harry Heth 1814 Feb 16 (Box 7)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 Feb 17 (Box 7)
- Letter from John Tayloe to Harry Heth 1814 Feb 19 (Box 7)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1814 Feb 26 (Box 7)
- Letter from D. M. Randolph to Harry Heth 1814 Mar 7 (Box 7)
- Letter from R. M. Heth to Harry Heth 1814 Mar 9 (Box 7)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1814 Mar 12 (Box 7)
- Letter from D. Meade to Harry Heth 1814 Mar 14 (Box 7)
- Letter from William Heth to Harry Heth 1814 Mar 15 (Box 7)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Robert B. Taylor 1814 Mar 23 (Box 7)
- Letter from D. Meade to Harry Heth 1814 Mar 23 (Box 8)
- Letter from Thomas S. Robion to Harry Heth 1814 Mar 23 (Box 8)
- Letter from John Cundiffe to Harry Heth 1814 Mar 24 (Box 8)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1814 Mar 27 (Box 8)
- Letter from Thomas Wilson to W. B. Randolph 1814 Mar 31 (Box 8)
- Letter from James Brown, Jr., to Harry Heth 1814 Apr 12 (Box 8)
- Letter from Joseph Tidball to Harry Heth 1814 Apr 15 (Box 8)
- Letter from Thomas Railey and Bros. To Harry Heth 1814 Apr 16 (Box 8)
- Letter from James Pleasants, Jr., to Harry Heth 1814 Apr 16 (Box 8)
- Letter from C. and R. Railey to Harry Heth 1814 Apr 17 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 Apr 18 (Box 8)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1814 Apr 9 (Box 8)
- Letter from Thomas Mann Randolph to Harry Heth 1814 Apr 17 (Box 8)
- Letter from Arthur Cooper to Harry Heth 1814 Apr 21 (Box 8)
- Letter from Eliza Meade to Harry Heth 1814 May 1 (Box 8)
- Letter from Samuel Woody to Harry Heth 1814 May 3 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 May 5 (Box 8)
- Extracts from Processioner's reports in 1800 and 1812 1814 May 7 (Box 8)
- Letter from H. G. Heth to Harry Heth 1814 May 10 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 May 11 (Box 8)
- Letter from John Tayloe to Harry Heth 1814 May 17 (Box 8)
- Letter from William B. Giles to Harry Heth 1814 May 18 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 May 20 (Box 8)
- Letter from H. G. Heth to Harry Heth 1814 May 22 (Box 8)
- Letter from N. Ellicott to Harry Heth 1814 May 23 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. Potts to Harry Heth 1814 May 25 (Box 8)
- Letter from John Cundiffe to Harry Heth 1814 May 29 (Box 8)
- Letter from N. Ellicott to Harry Heth 1814 May 30 (Box 8)
- Letter from D. Randolph to Harry Heth 1814 May 30 (Box 8)
- Harry, Heth vs M. W. Hancock, copy of commissioner's report 1814 May 30 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 Jun 8 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 Jun 11 (Box 8)
- Letter from Harry Heth to David Meade Randolph 1814 Jun 22 (Box 8)
- Letter from Sarah Prices to Harry Heth 1814 Jun 25 (Box 8)
- Letter from Edwin Corbin to Harry Heth 1814 Jun 27 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 Jun 27 (Box 8)
- Letter from Robert Taylor to Harry Heth 1814 Jul 2 (Box 8)
- Letter from Beverley Randolph 1814 Jul 7 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 Jul 7 (Box 8)
- Letter from William Jones, secretary of the Navy, to Harry Heth 1814 Jul 8 (Box 8)
- Letter from H. G. Heth to Harry Heth 1814 Jul 8 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. Roberts to Harry Heth 1814 Jul 15 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 Jul 22 (Box 8)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1814 Jul 31 (Box 8)
- Letter from Daniel P. Organ to Harry Heth 1814 Aug (Box 8)
- Letter from William B. Giles to Harry Heth 1814 Aug 3 (Box 8)
- Letter from Henry Heth to Harry Heth 1814 Aug 4 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. Potts to Harry Heth 1814 Aug 6 (Box 8)
- Letter from M. Randolph to Harry Heth 1814 Aug 17 (Box 8)
- Letter from H. G. Heth to Harry Heth 1814 Aug 9 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 Aug 11 (Box 8)
- Letter from Robert Pleasants to Harry Heth 1814 Aug 13 (Box 8)
- Letter from H. Randolph to Harry Heth 1814 Aug 16 (Box 8)
- Letter from David Street to Harry Heth 1814 Aug 17 (Box 8)
- Letter from Thomas W. Wilkinson to Harry Heth 1814 Aug 20 (Box 8)
- William Le Archer vs John Marshall, Harry Heth, and William G. Heth 1814 Sep 1 (Box 8)
- Letter from Virginia Heth to Mrs. Lavinia Randolph 1814 Sep 4 (Box 8)
- Letter from Harriet C. Robbins to Mrs. Lavinia Randolph 1814 Sep 7 (Box 8)
- Letter from John Heth 1814 Sep 18 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. Furguson, for Bolton, Watt and Co. to Messrs. Amgand Cornwall, and Co. 1814 Sep 23 (Box 8)
- Consolidated Cavalry Squadron Return Report 1814 Sep 30 (Box 8)
- Letter from Kitty Heth to Lavinia Randolph 1814 Oct 5 (Box 8)
- Articles of agreement, Beverly Randolph, Samuel G. Adams, and Emannuel Hoover 1814 Nov 16 (Box 8)
- Articles of co-partnery, Harry Heth, Samuel G. Adams, and Beverly Randolph 1814 Dec 3 (Box 8)
- Letter from H. Heth to S. M. Harrison 1814 Dec 6 (Box 8)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1814 Dec 9 (Box 8)
- Agreement, C. Mayes and Harry Heth 1814 Dec 17 (Box 8)
- Agreement, Wiley Jackson and H. Heth; S. Adams and Beverly Randolph 1814 Dec 21 (Box 8)
- Letter from Daniel Mays Railey to Harry Heth 1814 Dec 30 (Box 8)
- Accounts and receipts for 1814 1814 (Box 8)
- Letter from A. Lannehill to Harry Heth 1815 Jan 2 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1815 Jan 5 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1815 Jan 6 (Box 8)
- Letter from James Brown, Jr., to Beverly Randolph 1815 Jan 13 (Box 8)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Beverly Randolph 1815 Jan 24 (Box 8)
- Power of attorney - Beverly Randolph and Samuel G. Adams to Harry Heth 1815 Jan 26 (Box 8)
- Letter from Robert Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Jan 30 (Box 8)
- Letter from Thomas Railey to Harry Heth 1815 Feb 14 (Box 8)
- Letter from Ann G. Morris to Harry Heth 1815 Feb 14 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. Barber to Harry Heth 1815 Feb 15 (Box 8)
- Agreement between Beverly Randolph and Hugh Graham 1815 Feb 15 (Box 8)
- Letter from Morgan Neville to Harry Heth 1815 Feb 16 (Box 8)
- Letter from Henry Foxall to Messrs. Heth and Randolph 1815 Feb 21 (Box 8)
- Letter from Vincent Gray to Harry Heth 1815 Feb 22 (Box 8)
- Letter from H. Heth to Henry Heth 1815 Feb 26 (Box 8)
- Letter from F. James to Beverly Randolph 1815 Feb 28 (Box 8)
- Letter from William Dodge and Son to Heth and Randolph 1815 Feb 28 (Box 8)
- Letter from Fontaine Maury to Harry Heth 1815 Feb 19 (Box 8)
- Letter from William Heth to Harry Heth 1815 Mar 7 (Box 8)
- Letter from Abraham Wih, Jr., to Harry Heth 1815 Mar 7 (Box 8)
- Letter from Peter F. Smith to B. Randolph 1815 Mar 9 (Box 8)
- Letter from William Dodge & Son to Harry Heth 1815 Mar 10 (Box 8)
- Letter from William Dodge & Son to Harry Heth 1815 Mar 11 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. Colquhoun to Harry Heth 1815 Mar 14 (Box 8)
- Letter from John Potts to Beverly Randolph 1815 Mar 18 (Box 8)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Mssrs. Benten & Heth 1815 Mar 20 (Box 8)
- Agreement between Nathaniel Bosworth & Beverley Randolph & Co. 1815 Mar 20 (Box 8)
- Letter from Samuel Shrewsbury to Harry Heth 1815 Mar 20 (Box 8)
- Letter from Alex Fraser to Heth & Randolph 1815 Mar 21 (Box 8)
- Letter from William Dodge & Son to Harry or Richard Hughes 1815 Mar 21 (Box 8)
- Letter from E. Cort to Harry Heth 1815 Mar 22 (Box 8)
- Letter from John Randolph of Roanoke to Harry Heth 1815 Mar 29 (Box 8)
- Letter from William Heth to Harry Heth 1815 Mar 30 (Box 8)
- Letter from E. H. Randolph to Beverley Randolph 1815 Mar 31 (Box 8)
- Letter from Robert Pleasants to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 1 (Box 8)
- Letter from Archibald Freeland to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 1 (Box 8)
- Letter from B. Dandridge to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 1 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 2 (Box 8)
- Letter from Joseph Railey to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 2 (Box 8)
- Letter from William Heth to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 2 (Box 8)
- Letter from John Thade to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 3 (Box 8)
- Letter from Richard Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 3 (Box 8)
- Letter from John Potts to [?] 1815 Apr 4 (Box 8)
- Letter from William & Robert Steele to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 4 (Box 8)
- Letter from Robert Harris to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 4 (Box 8)
- Letter from Samuel Turner to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 5 (Box 8)
- Letter from Jacob Michany to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 6 (Box 8)
- Letter from William B. Randolph to Mssrs. Heth & Randolph 1815 Apr 8 (Box 8)
- Letter from Samuel Turner to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 8 (Box 8)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 10 (Box 8)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 11 (Box 8)
- Letter from James P. Cocke to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 11 (Box 8)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 11 (Box 8)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 12 (Box 8)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 12 (Box 8)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 12 (Box 8)
- Letter from William M. Heth to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 13 (Box 8)
- Letter from Elizabeth Railey to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 14 (Box 8)
- Letter from Catherine to Beverly Randolph 1815 Apr 14 (Box 8)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 15 (Box 8)
- Letter from Ann G. Morris to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 19 (Box 8)
- Agreement between John Murchee, Edward Johnson, & Charles Cundiffe 1815 Apr 24 (Box 8)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 16 (Box 9)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 16 (Box 9)
- Letter from A. Tannehill to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 16 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 17 (Box 9)
- Letter from Daniel Mayo Railey to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 18 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 19 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Cunningham & Co. to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 20 (Box 9)
- Letter from Peter F. Smith to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 20 (Box 9)
- Agreement between Johnson & Cundiffe, John Cundiffe & Needler Robins 1815 Apr 21 (Box 9)
- Agreement between Edward Johnston & Harry Heth 1815 Apr 21 (Box 9)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 24 (Box 9)
- Letter from A. Tannehill to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 22 (Box 9)
- Letter from Nathaniel Bosworth to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 22 (Box 9)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 25 (Box 9)
- Letter from Thomas Miller to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 25 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert M. Heth to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 28 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 28 (Box 9)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 28 (Box 9)
- Letter from William M. Heth to Harry Heth 1815 Apr 29 (Box 9)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 May (Box 9)
- Letter from Ann G. Morris to Harry Heth 1815 May (Box 9)
- Agreement of William H. Wash 1815 May 1 (Box 9)
- Letter from Francis Minor to Harry Heth 1815 May 2 (Box 9)
- Letter from B. Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 May 2 (Box 9)
- Letter from Thomas W. Wilkins to Harry Heth 1815 May 4 (Box 9)
- Letter from Thomas Clapton to Harry Heth 1815 May 5 (Box 9)
- Letter from Morgan Neville to Harry Heth 1815 May 5 (Box 9)
- Letter from Neil McCoule to Harry Heth 1815 May 7 (Box 9)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Beverly Randolph 1815 May 7 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 May 8 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to [?] 1815 May 8 (Box 9)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Dr. Triplett 1815 May 8 (Box 9)
- Letter from B. Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 May 9 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 May 9 (Box 9)
- Letter from Charles Tompkins to Harry Heth 1815 May 15 (Box 9)
- Letter from Mary Lawrence to Harry Heth 1815 May 16 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 1815 May 18 (Box 9)
- Letter from Frank S. Sampson to Harry Heth 1815 May 21 (Box 9)
- Letter from C. H. Deer to Harry Heth 1815 May 21 (Box 9)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 May 23 (Box 9)
- Letter from A. Tannehill to Harry Heth 1815 May 26 (Box 9)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1815 May 27 (Box 9)
- Letter from William Barrel to Harry Heth 1815 May 27 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 1815 May 28 (Box 9)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 May 30 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Porterfield to Harry Heth 1815 May 30 (Box 9)
- Letter from L. Hollingsworth to Harry Heth 1815 May 31 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Pleasants to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 2 (Box 9)
- Letter from Ann Heth to Beverly Randolph 1815 Jun 2 (Box 9)
- Letter from John Tandy to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 3 (Box 9)
- Letter from Samuel G. Adams to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 4 (Box 9)
- Letter from Samuel G. Adams to Beverly Randolph 1815 Jun 4 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 5 (Box 9)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 5 (Box 9)
- Letter from officers of the Manchester Cavalry 1815 Jun 8 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 5 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Taylor to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 6 (Box 9)
- Letter from David Street to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 8 (Box 9)
- Letter from Richard Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 9 (Box 9)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 9 (Box 9)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Beverly Randolph 1815 Jun 11 (Box 9)